Greenbaum, Marcia Papers 6091
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Texas International Airlines Pilots Group and Continental Airlines Pilots Group in the matter of Pilot Seniority Integration: contains: Alpha merger policy, proposals, employment data, entitlements, and portion of master file. 1983. (Box 59)
  - Volume VIII Age 60 Downbidding to Flight Engineer, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    Substantial damage to left edge of file
  - Documents Relating to Air Line Pilots Association International, 1980-1983 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    Damage to left side of documents
  - F/E-S/O Third Crew Member and ALPA Constitution and By-Laws, 1977-1983 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - CAL/TXI/ALPA Integration Award 7/25/83., 1983-1986 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Plaintiffs, v. Air Lines Pilots Association International and Continental Air Lines, Inc., Defendants, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - ALPA International Int. ARB. 83 Continental Air/Texas Intl. Merger of Pilots Seniority Lists, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Draft and Notes, 1974-1975 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - ALPA/TXI/CAL Pilot Seniority Integration Notes, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Basic Documents and Pay Comparisons (Box 59, Folder 12)
- Texas International Airlines Pilots Group and Continental airlines Pilots. 1983: contains: Master file with notes and drafts, correspondence, and prior arbitration awards.. (Box 60)
  - Merger Policies and Other Docs Relating to Texas International Airlines and USA Civil Aeronautics Board, 1981-1982 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - ALPA/TXI/CAL Pilot Seniority Integration Chronologies, 1975-1982 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - ALPA/TXI/CAL Merger Working Papers, 1981-1982 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - ALPA, 1985 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - CAL Trial Exhibits Cross-Referenced for Tr. Pages and Witness Testimony and Other docs., 1978 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - TXI Certified List and CAL Certified List, 1983 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - ALPA/TXI/CAL Pilot Seniority Integration Seniority Proposals & Printouts, 1983 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Lists (not proposals) Print out and Graphic of Date-Of-Hire & Vos 1-1-83, CAL/TXI DoH List 1-1-88, CAL/TXI ALOS 1-1-88, 1983 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Continental Non-Active Pilots, 1983 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Docs. Relating to Texas International Pilots, 1981 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Revised List of Air Line Pilots (Folder 1 of 2), 1981 (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Texas International Pilots and Certified UST Continental Pilots, 1983 (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Docs. Relating to TXI Pilots (Box 60, Folder 13)
- Texas International Airlines Pilots Group and Continental Airlines Pilots 1983: contains: pre-merger and merger history, scenarios and projections, and impact of deregulation of airline industry.. (Box 61)
  - TXI Pre Merger C.B. Benefits and Pay Comparison, 1983 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - TXI Renewal and Property Plans, 1983 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - CAL Prosperity Plan and Prosperity Plan Bid Predictions Jan 1983 Mg 1987, 1982 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Fence Agreement Combined Working Agreement, 1981-1982 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - History of TXI and CAL, 1981 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - History of TXI Acquisition of CAL, 1982 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Scenarios Absent Merger Incl. Esop-E chel, 1982 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Financial Review of the Majors (Rebuttal to TXI 6500 Series), 1982 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Continental Pilots "C" Exhibit, 1981-1983 (Box 61, Folder 9)
- Texas International Airlines Pilots Group and Continental Airlines Pilots 1983: contains: pre-merger and merger history, scenarios and projections, and impact of deregulation of airline industry.. (Box 62)
  - Volume VI-Part A Impact of Deregulation, 1983 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Volume VI-Part B Impact of Deregulation, 1983 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Rebuital Continental Pilots' Exhibits R-101 To R-115, 1978 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Continental Pilots' Exhibits R-700 Series, 1978-1982 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Index and Index of Surrebuttal Exhibits, 1981 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Pre Merger Furlough Docs. Relating to Airlines, 1980-1983 (Box 62, Folder 6)
- Texas International Airlines Pilots Group and Continental Airlines Pilots 1983: contains: transcripts box A which includes Volumes IA-- XVI B. (Box 63)
  - Vol. I Section I Texas International Airlines Pilots Group, and Continental Air Lines Pilots Group, 1983 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Vol. I Section II, 1983 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Vol. II Reagan Jackson Secor Browne Ronald Cosgrove, 1983 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Vol. III Secor Browne Charles Kurth, 1983 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Vol. IV Charles Kirth 760, 1983 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Vol. V Charles Kurth Glenn Smellhouse, 1983 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Vol. VIA Witnesses: Michael B. Ferrara Jim McCartney, 1983 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Vol. VIB Witness: Jim McCartney, 1983 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Vol. VII Witnesses: Jim McCartney, J.V. Sclifo, Theodore Vass, 1983 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Vol. VIII Witnesses: Theodore Vass Reagan Jackson, 1983 (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Vol. IX Witness: James McCartney, 1983 (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Vol. X Witnesses: George H. Turner, 1983 (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Vol. XIA Witnesses: George H. Turner, 1983 (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Vol. XIB Witnesses: George H. Turner, 1983 (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - Vol. XIC Section 3 Turner, 1983 (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - Vol. XII-3001 In the Matter of Pilot Seniority Integration Witnesses: Capt. Guy Casey, 1983 (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - Vol. XIII In the Matter of Pilot Seniority Integration Witnesses: Capt. Guy Casey and Capt. Paul Eckel, 1983 (Box 63, Folder 17)
  - Vol. XIV-3621 In the Matter of Pilot Seniority Integration Witnesses: Capt. Duane Barton, 1983 (Box 63, Folder 18)
  - Vol. XV-3901 In the Matter of Pilot Seniority Integration Witnesses: Carl M. Miller George Turner (Recalled0, 1983 (Box 63, Folder 19)
  - Vol. XVI 4201and XVI-B 4261 In the Matter of Pilot Seniority Integration Witnesses: George Turner and Charles Arthur, 1983 (Box 63, Folder 20)
  - Box b3 "Index of Folders", 1983 (Box 63, Folder 21)
- Texas International Airlines Pilots Group and Continental Airlines Pilots 1983: contains:transcripts box B, includes Volumes XVII--XXVIII B. (Box 64)
  - "Index of Folders" box 64, 1983 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Texas International Airlines Pilots Group and Continental Air Lines Pilots Group, 1983 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Tx. Internat. Airlines Pilots Group and Cont. Air Lines Pilots Group Vol. 2BA, 1983 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - TX Internat. Airline Pilots Group and Cont. Airlines Pilots Group Vol. 27, 1983 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Tx. Internat. And Cont. Air Line Vol. 26, 1983 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - TX Internat. And Cont. Air Lines Vol. 25, 1983 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - TX Internat. Airlines Pilots Group And Cont. Air Lines Vol. 24, 1983 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - TX Internat. And Cont. Air Lines Vol. 23, 1983 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - TX Internat. And Cont. AirLines Vo.22, 1983 (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Tx. Internat. And Cont. Airlines Vol. 21, 1983 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - TX Internat. And Cont. Airlines Vol. 20, 1983 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - TX Internat and Cont. Airlines Vol. 19, 1983 (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - TX Internat. And Cont. Airlines Vol. 18 B, 1983 (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - TX Internat. And Cont. Airlines 18 A, 1983 (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Tx. Internat. And Cont. Airlines Vol. 17, 1983 (Box 64, Folder 15)
- United Airlines/ALPA, AFA; United Airlines/ IAMAW 1974- 1979. (Box 65)
  - Agreement btwn. United Air Lines Inc. and The Internat. Assoc. of Machinists and Aerospace Workers and Flight Attendant, 1972- 1978 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - United Air Lines MEC 3-74 ARB and ALPA CHI 21-74F ALPA, Stewards & Stewardesses Div., 1974 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - United Air Lines SBA # 5-74 and ALPA #CHI ALPA, Stewards and Stewardesses Div., 1974 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - United Air Lines Inc. ALPA and SBA Gr. 14-74 CHI ALPA, Steward & Stewardesses Div., 1974-1975 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - United Air Lines, Inc. SBA #SEA 7-74 and ALPA #CHI-239-74 F ARB ALPA, Stewards & Stewardesses Division, 1974- 1975 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - United Air Lines Inc. April 10-11 and ARB-75 ALPA, Stewardesses & Steward Division, 1974-1975 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - United Air Lines, Inc. May 14-15 75 and Lax 28-74, CHI 247-74F ARB ALPA, Stewardesses & Steward Div., 1974- 1975 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - United Air Lines Inc. July 24-25, 1975 and SFO 29-75 CHI 137-75 F Assn. of Flight Attendants (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - United Air Lines Inc. June 14-20 July 14 and EWR 1-75 CHI 2975 F ALPA, Stewardesses & Steward Div., 1975 (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - United Airlines, Inc., 1975 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Hearing on the Grievance, 1975 (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - United Airlines and Assoc. Flight Attendants' Div., 1973-1975 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Hearing on the Grievance, 1975 (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - Air Line Pilots Association, International, Steward and Stewardess Division, Complaint, and United Air Lines, Inc., Respondent RE: Grievance, 1975 (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - United Air Lines (Stewardess-Steward) System Board of Adjustment Grievances, 1970 (Box 65, Folder 15)
  - United Air Lines, Inc. Cot. 1975 ARB and CHI-31-75F, EWR-3-75 ALPA, AFA Division (Hair), 1970-1976 (Box 65, Folder 16)
- United Airlines/ALPA, AFA; United Airlines/ IAMAW 1974- 1979. (Box 66)
  - United Air Lines Chicago and MIA 10-75 ARB 1976 Assn. of Flight Attendants, 1975-1976 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Univ. of Connecticut Intl. ARB 1989 and AAA #1230-00237-89 New K CSFT, Local 3695, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - United Air Lines Los Angeles and LAX 12-75 ARB 1976 Assn. of Flight Attendants, 1975 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Documents Relating to the University of Connecticut Board- Arbitration, Reclassification upgradings and pool, 1990-1992 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - United Air Lines Los Angeles and SFO 41-75 ARB 1976 Assn. Of Flight Attendants (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Union Reply Brief University of Connecticut vs University of Connecticut Professional Employees, Local 3695 Case No: 12 300 0237 89, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - United Airlines, Inc. Oct. 14 and Sys. Bd. MEC 9-76 ARB 1976 Assn. of Flight Attendants, 1974-1977 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - The University of Connecticut and The University of Connecticut Professional Employees Association, Local 3695, CSFT, AFT, AFL-CIO, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - United Airlines, Inc. Oct. 211976 and Sys. Bd. Mec 9-76 ARB 1976 Assn. of Flight Attendants A, 1975-1979 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - United Airlines, Inc. and Asnn. Of Flight Attendants 555.Bd. Mec 9-76 ARB 1976 Oct. 21, 22 1976 B, 1975 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    Contains photographs
  - Hearing on Mec Grievance 8-76, Before the United Airlines Flight Attendants' System Board of Adjustment, 1976 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - United Airlines Inc. and UAL AFA Sys. Bd. DCA 8-76 J. Day Assn. of Flight Attendants. ALPA, 1976 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - United Air Lines, Inc. Oct. 1975 ARB and CHI-37-74F, SFO-3-74 ALPA, APA Division, 1974-1978 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Hearing on the Grievance of Diane Roberstson, Before the United Airlines Flight Attendants, 1975-1976 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - United Airlines Inc. and Gr. #99392 ARB 1977 Intl. Assn. of Machinists, 1976-1977 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - United Airlines Direct and Griev. #90856-SFO ARB 1977 Intl. Assn. of Machinists (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - United Air Lines; Inc. and Direct ARB 1977 IAM, District 141, 1977-1978 (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - United Air Lines, Inc. ARB 78 and Gr. #110850-SFO.Discharge IAMAW of, 1978-1979 (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - United Air Lines Linc 1978 and Gr. #107722-29 LGA Direct ARB Intl. Assn. of Machinists, District 141 (Box 66, Folder 15)
- University of Connecticut Board of Trustees and University of Conn. Professional Employees Association Local 3695, CSFT, AFT, AFL-CIO AAA# 12 3000 00237 89 1989. (Box 67)
  - Univ. of Connecticut Int. ARB 1989 and AAA #1230-00237-89 New K SFT, Local 3695, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Docs Relating to the University of Connecticut Board-Arbitration Reclassification upgrading's and pool, 1989-1992 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Union Reply Brief University of Connecticut vs University of Connecticut Professional Employees, Local 3695 Case No: 12 300 0237 89, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - The University of Connecticut and The University of Connecticut Professional Employees Association Local 3695, CSF, AFT, AFL-CIO AAA Case No: 12 300 00237 89, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Reply Brief of the University of Connecticut in the Binding Arbitration between the University and the Professional Employees Assoc. AAA Case No. 12-300-00237-89, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Last Best Offer Proposals of the University of Connecticut in Interest Arbitration for the Agreement with the Professional Employees Association (UCPEA), 1989-1992 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Interest Arbitration between The University of Connecticut and The University of Connecticut Professional Employees Association #3695, CSFT, AFT, AFL-CIO, 1989-1990 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - The University of Connecticut Bulletin- Course Catalog for Undergraduates and Graduates, 1989 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Economics- UCPEAX2 The University of Connecticut and The University of Connecticut Professional Employees Assoc. #3695, CSFT, AFT, AFL-CIO, 1989-1992 (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Docs. Relating to the University of Connecticut, 1987 (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Merit Exhibits The University of Connecticut and The University of Connecticut Professional Employees Association #3695, CSFT,AFT, AFL-CIO by Union 40.1-40.69, 1988-1989 (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - Tuition & Fees Waivers, 1987-1990 (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - University of Connecticut Documents Relating to Finances and Tuition, 1987-1988 (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - University of Connecticut Docs. Relating to Finances (Folder 1 of 2), 1988-1989 (Box 67, Folder 14)
  - University of Connecticut Docs. Relating to Finances (Folder 1 of 2), 1988-1989 (Box 67, Folder 15)
  - Booklets Relating to Agreements between the State of Connecticut and other -, 1989-1990 (Box 67, Folder 16)
- 1) University of Conn. Board of Trustees and U. of Conn. Professional Employees Assn. Local 3695, CSFT, AFT, AFL-CIO AAA# 12 3000 00237 89 1989; 2) University of Massachusetts and MTA mediation. 1979; 3) U.S. Postal Service and American Postal Worke (Box 68)
  - Contracts and Agreements between Diff. Branches of State/Univ. of Connecticut Gov. Organizations, 1985-1990 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - P-1, 1985-1990 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - University of Massachusetts and MTA Mediation 79, 1980 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - University of Massachusetts and MTA Mediation 1979, 1979-1980 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - U.S. Postal Service ARB 82 and N8M-1J-D 21649 NAMH, 1982 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - U.S. Postal Service and N8M-1J-D 27281 ARB 82 NAMH, 1982 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - U.S. Postal Service and N1M-1J-D 3739 ARB 82 NAMH, 1981-1992 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - U.S. Postal Service ARB 83 and N1C-1A-D 3337; 3409 A.P.W.U., 1981-1983 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - U.S. Postal Service and N1C-1M-D 4040 ARB 83 A.P.W.U., 1981-1983 (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - U.S. Postal Service and N1C-1R-D 7740 ARB 83 A.P.W.U., 1982-1983 (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - U.S. Postal Service and N1S-1M-D 4599 ARB 83 A.P.W.U., 1982-1983 (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - U.S. Postal Service and N1C-1A-D 5076 A.P.W.U. ARB 83, 1982-1983 (Box 68, Folder 12)
  - U.S. Postal Service ARB 83 and N1C-1N-D 11540 A.P.W.U., 1982-1983 (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - U.S. Postal Service and N1C-1N-D 10017 ARB 83 A.P.W.U., 1983 (Box 68, Folder 14)
  - U.S. Postal Service and N1C-1N-D 1026 S. Layton A.P.W.U. ARB 83, 1982-1983 (Box 68, Folder 15)
  - U.S. Postal Service and N8C-1A-D 26777 A.P.W.U., 1983 (Box 68, Folder 16)
  - U.S. Postal Service and NIT-1M-D II48 D.Marone A.P.W.U. Removal ARB 83, 1982-1983 (Box 68, Folder 17)
  - U.S. Postal Service and N1T-1M-D 6149 A.P.W.U. ARB 83, 1982-1983 (Box 68, Folder 18)
- US Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union 1982- 1983. (Box 69)
  - U.S. Postal Service and N1C-1n-d 7225 ARB 83 A.P.W.U., 1980-1983 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - U.S. Postal Service and N1C-1A-D 5397 A.P.W.U. ARB 83, 1982-1983 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - U.S. Postal Service ARB 83 and N1N-1N-D 18718; 18719 N.A.L.C. R. Burger, 1982-1983 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - U.S. Postal Service and N1N-1M-D 18244 ARB 83 N.A.L.C., 1983-1984 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - U.S. Postal Service ARB 83 and N1N-1A-D 7297 N.A.L.C., 1983 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - U.S. Postal Service and N1N-1E-D 16922 ARB 83 N.A.L.C., 1982-1984 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - U.S. Postal Service and N1N-1J-D 16651 ARB 83 N.A.L.C., 1983-1984 (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - U.S. Postal Service and N1N-1E-D 16589 ARB 83 N.A.L.C., 1984 (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - U.S. Postal Service ARB 83 and N1N-1A-D 7114 N.A.L.C., 1980-1983 (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - United Postal Service Cases-1983 (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - U.S. Postal Service and ARB 82 N8T-1A-D 22989 APWU, 1981-1982 (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - U.S. Postal Service A-D 23437 and ARB 82 N8T-1A-D 23438 APWU, 1981-1982 (Box 69, Folder 12)
  - U.S. Postal Service 23934 FS and ARB 82 N8T-1A-D 23949 J Rem APWU, 1981-1982 (Box 69, Folder 13)
  - U.S. Postal Service and ARB 82 N8C-1A-D 21780 APWU, 1982 (Box 69, Folder 14)
  - U.S. Postal Service 22 951-N and ARB 82 N8C-1J-D 23241-RJ APWU, 1982 (Box 69, Folder 15)
  - U.S. Postal Service and ARB 82 N8C-1A-D 20381 APWU D. Kidd U.S. Postal Service and ARB 82 N8C-1A-D 23926 APWU, 1982 (Box 69, Folder 16)
  - U.S. Postal Service ARB 82 and N8C-1E-D 23369 APWU 23369, 1983 (Box 69, Folder 17)
  - U.S. Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union ARB N8C-1-E-23369, 1982 (Box 69, Folder 18)
  - U.S. Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union ARB N8C-1-E-23369, 1982 (Box 69, Folder 19)
  - U.S. Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union ARB N8C-7-E-23369, 1982 (Box 69, Folder 20)
  - U.S. Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union ARB N8C-1-E-23369, 1982 (Box 69, Folder 21)
  - U.S. Postal Service and ARB 82 N8C-1A-D 26220, 1981-1982 (Box 69, Folder 22)
  - U.S. Postal Service and N1C-10-D 582; 8351 ARB 83, 1981-1983 (Box 69, Folder 23)
  - U.S. Postal Service Vaccaro and ARB 82 APWU N8C-10-D 22813, 1982 (Box 69, Folder 24)
  - U.S. Postal Service and ARB 82 N8C-1E-D 23267 APWU, 1982 (Box 69, Folder 25)
- 1) U.S. Postal Service and American Postal Workers Union 1982-1983; 2) Worcester, City of and Worcester Police Officials Association. PF 52-1979. (Box 70)
  - U.S. Postal Service ARB 82 and N1N-1M-D 7133 N.A.L.C., 1983 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - U.S. Postal Service and ARB 82 #N8N-1A-D 26494 NALC, 1982 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - U.S. Postal Service ARB 82 and N1N-1A-D 6579 & 6581 N.A.L.C., 1982 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - U.S. Postal Service and ARB 82 N8N-1A-D 23269 ES N8N-1A-D 238559 D NALC, 1981-1982 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - U.S. Postal Service Rodrigued and ARB 82 N8N-1E-C 19453 NALC, 1981-1982 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - U.S. Postal Service W. Campbell and ARB 82 NAMH N8M-1A-D 21893, 1980-1982 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - U.S. Postal Service and ARB 82 N8M-1A-D 21487 NAMH, 1981-1982 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - City of Worcester/Police Officials Fact Finding Report July 10, 1979 (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - City Of Worcester and PF-52-1979 FF Worcester Police Officials Assoc. (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Fact Finding Worcester/Worcester Police Officials City Exhibits (Folder 1 of 3), 1975-1978 (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Fact Finding Worcester/Worcester Police Officials City Exhibits (Folder 2 of 3), 1975-1978 (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Fact Finding Worcester/Worcester Police Officials City Exhibits (Folder 3 of 3), 1975-1978 (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Fact Finding Worcester/Worcester Police Officials Assn. Exhibits (Folder 1 of 3), 1976-1978 (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Fact Finding Worcester/Worcester Police Officials Assn. Exhibits (Folder 2 of 3), 1976-1978 (Box 70, Folder 14)
  - Fact Finding Worcester/Worcester Police Officials Assn. Exhibits (Folder 3 of 3), 1976-1978 (Box 70, Folder 15)
- AFL-CIO-- NY State Labor Law. (Box 71)
  - AFL-CIO, 1987 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Antitrust Laws, 1955-1961 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Automation, 1959-1963 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Collective Bargaining, 1951-1968 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Corruption and Racketeering, 1958 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Economics, 1962 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Employee Rights, 1965-1973 (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Ethics Dispute Resolution, 1973-1983 (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Employment- Manpower, 1963 (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Health and Welfare, 1966-1984 (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - Hospitals, 1963 (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Hours- SWW, 1962-1964 (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - Work Hours- Satisfaction, 1977 (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - ILR General, 1950-1958 (Box 71, Folder 14)
  - ILR Research, 1963-1964 (Box 71, Folder 15)
  - ILGWU, 1959-1974 (Box 71, Folder 16)
  - Labor Law, 1966-1972 (Box 71, Folder 17)
  - Labor Management Coop Program, 1986-1987 (Box 71, Folder 18)
  - Labor Markets, 1956 (Box 71, Folder 19)
  - Labor Union History, 1958-1962 (Box 71, Folder 20)
  - Landrum-Griffin ACT, 1959 (Box 71, Folder 21)
  - Management Rights, 1966 (Box 71, Folder 22)
  - National Labor Relations Board, 1955 (Box 71, Folder 23)
  - New York State Labor Law, 1959-1964 (Box 71, Folder 24)
- NY State Labor Relations Board-- Wages. (Box 72)
  - New York State Labor Relations Board, 1956-1961 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Pensions and Retirement, 1974 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Personnel Administration, 1954-1969 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Railroads, 1962 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Research, 1961-1962 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Seniority, 1962 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Steel Prices, Strikes, Industry, 1960-1962 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Stress and Other Articles (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Strikes, 1967-1983 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Strike Prohibitions, 1958-1967 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Taft Hartley, 1950-1959 (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Teamsters-Hoffa, 1959 (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - Transit, 1960 (Box 72, Folder 13)
  - Unemployment ** UC and Sub, 1955-1969 (Box 72, Folder 14)
  - Union Democracy, 1960-1964 (Box 72, Folder 15)
  - Wages, 1960-1971 (Box 72, Folder 16)
  - Diff. Labor Agreements, 1976-1997 (Box 72, Folder 17)
  - International Industrial Booklets, 1979-1981 (Box 72, Folder 18)
  - Trade Union Structure The Work Life Review and Other Docs. Relating to Labor, 1975-1978 (Box 72, Folder 19)
- NAA 1985- 1992. (Box 73)
  - National Academy of Arbitrators Board of Governors 1990 Policy Handbook (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - National Academy of Arbitrators- The Chronicle, 1989-1992 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - National Academy of Arbitrators 1992 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - NAA Continuing Education Dearborn, MI-Nov. 1-4, 1990 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - NAA Continuing Education 1992 Chicago Hyatt Regency 10/28/92 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - National Academy of Arbitrators 1992 Annual Meeting May 25-31, 1992 Atlanta Ga. (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - National Academy of Arbitrators 1991 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - National Academy of Arbitrators Dues Non-Payment Policy, 1990 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - National Academy of Arbitrators Program Committee, 1990 (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - National Academy of Arbitrators May, 1990 San Diego, CA (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - 1990 National Academy of Arbitrators Vice President (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - NAA Vice President File 1989 Board of Governors Meetings (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - NAA Research Committee 1989 Chapter for Book, 1989-1990 (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - National Academy of Arbitration Research Committee 1985-86, 1986-1987 (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - Arbitrators- Education Training and Development, 1948-1954 (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - Arbitrators as Lawyers, 1976-1981 (Box 73, Folder 16)
  - NAA Research Committee Survey Book Introduction, 1978-1989 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - Frequency Runs for NAA Data (Box 73, Folder 18)
- SPIDR (Society of Professionals in Dispute Resolution): 1986 and earlier. (Box 74)
  - SPIDR Local Chapters, 1983-1986 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - SPIDR Grants, 1984-1987 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - SPIDR Chicago Hotel Arrangements, 1985-1986 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - SPIDR Travel Chicago, 1986 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - SPIDR- List of names and Docs. Relating to Conference, 1986 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - SPIDR Abner Award Committee 1986, 1984 (Box 74, Folder 6)